In this video clip, I will be talking about electrical safety.
First off, it is important to know that the cord is the life line of your tool.
You want to make sure you keep your cord in good working condition.
Make sure that there are no cracks or tears in it.
Any type of damage to the chord is just leading to disaster.
For your tool to be properly grounded, you want to make sure that you have all three prongs on the plug.
This will insure maximum safety when using your tool.
Now, although it is not recommended to use an extension chord, if you do have a situation where you need to use one to reach your location, you want to make sure that the extension chord is of the proper rating.
And lastly, you never want to abuse the chord.
You never want to carry the tool by the chord.
And you just want to take extra care when handling your tool and the chord.